Hello everyone, how are you all? I am
your own personal advisor Amita Sharma, and you are
watching this real. The credit for today's video goes to
this comment by Mr. Rahul Pathak, who is looking at his skin.
Mr. Pathak wants us to
tell you about Aditya Birla Sun Life Insurance's Should Income Plan. Pathak ji,
thank you very much for this comment.
Before starting the video, I would like to inform you
that every video on the channel
comes according to your suggestions, questions and comments. If you want us to keep
bringing videos as per your personal suggestions in the future, then please
like this video, share it with your friends,
subscribe to the channel
and turn on the notification bell so that
whenever the latest video is released on the channel, you get to
know about it. Tell us in the comment section that you
want the next video to be on the topic.
Now, without wasting any time, let us understand the details of Aditya Birla
Sun Life Insurance Company Limited's Should
Income Plan. This
plan is non-participating and gives regular income. This Should Income
Plan has no connection with the market.
Performance slips or dance TV will
not affect your premium.
Whatever you pay, in simple words, this is a
guaranteed money back plan. Now, what kind of guaranteed
money back plan is this? See, if you do
not have the required amount to take a pension plan
or to
generate income for retirement or for
child education, then
in this plan, you can invest money in it and later, after
completion of the policy term, you can get
money for your retirement and child education.
This is also its selling point. In
this plan, you get two types of
options - Income Benefit and Income
Benefit with Return of Premium. Now, the
term of Income Benefit is different. To go
to the cigarette area, the first
thing that comes to mind is the entry limit of
your child. You can take the plan. The
minimum entry limit is 5 years and the maximum is
60 years. The limit for children and teenagers ranges
from 18 years. The minimum age is 5 lakh
and the maximum is 5.5 lakh.  It means that if you invest
Rs. 5.5 lakhs then you will be able to
take it, at least you have to invest Rs. 500 annually, there is
no maximum limit on the rules and regulations because it depends on the
underwriting, telecommunications and regulation of the policy,
which is profited by the board,
now we will talk about the policy
term, premium payment term and these computers,
with the one year policy system,
you get premium payment for 6 years
and with the one year policy system, you
get the option of 25 years, 20 years and 30 years income
policy, in which you can choose an option of
9 years with post-mortem and the
premium paying term of 20 years is 25 years, you
get the option of 30 years incomplete, in which you
can choose one, if you
take a 13 year policy system, then the
premium payment will be for 12 years, which means you will have to pay premium for 12 years,
you get an income period of 20 years and 25 years and today we will
talk about the income period, so mode of income  The
benefit is your annual benefit,
it is included in the mind and monthly,
you can decide as per what you feel is right, at the
time of taking the policy itself, if you take the income benefit
in installments, then annually
you will get 100% of the income benefit
in installments, but if you
take it quarterly then you will get 40% of this benefit, if you take it quarterly then you will
get 24.5 percent, if you
take it monthly then you will get 8 percent of the
annual income benefit,
okay, yes, let's talk about the
benefit in the plan, the first thing that will come to mind
here is the death benefit because the death
benefit is during the policy term,
you remain undercover in it because later
your interim starts, right,
if death happens then you will get the net,
right, support has been expressed,
ten times your Android ice cream or one hundred and fifty
times the premium you have paid, whichever is basic
or spoon and whichever is higher among these, then that will be given to the
nominee, okay,
now see this screenshot that I have
posted, of this  You can also get it on the website, so in the
death benefit it
is clearly written that during the policy term the consequences
remain covered, so its clear meaning is this, right
here itself I am confirming to you that when the
body system dies, then incomplete will start,
when incomplete will start, then
in whichever mode you have selected, you will get the
right to receive the income benefit in that mode only
and you have the option
that if you want, normally the health
benefit can be received in annual or monthly installments, the
period for that will be
10 years, if the
nominee gets the death benefit in installments, then if you take it
annually then normally he will
get 12.02 2% of the death benefit amount, if you
take it monthly then he will get 1.02 1%, total if
you see then
108 will be 20.22 percent of the death benefit amount, which will be
received in the form of 10 benefits, if you have
chosen annual mode then  If monthly
investment is done then 22.58 percent of the total death benefit amount will be given to
them in installments
that we will get the death benefit. Now we have to know
what is the sum shot in this plan
because if we saw in the wiser, then I
understood only whichever of the three was there, so I have
understood till one option that in the
advised premium, we will make
this agreement and your agreement factors fair, if the
age is 30 years then 13 which
went here will become agreement factor,
now after passing the agreement, please read this, all the
factors are written on the mother, now it comes to the
income option, that is, plan
option, we are talking about income benefit,
okay, in what way will they get the
benefit if the age is 50 years or less
and the annual
premium is 1 lakh rupees or
more and if the premium
payment term is taken for 12 years and along with that if the
income benefit period is taken for 20 years, then the
annual advised premium is the basic
premium in which  You have edited the set, you will keep
getting 125 percent of it for 20 years as
income benefits because no matter how much the plate,
if we take the income benefit the return of
premium option, then you
can read its full skin on your skin in the video chat, we assume
that the age is up to 50 years and the annual
premium is Rs 1 lakh and
if we take the premium
on the minimum term of 12 years here and we take the income
benefit period term of 20 years, then you will keep getting
income benefit of the advance premium at the rate of 93.7 percent for the
next 20 years, we have taken the income period
here, now see here you have
seen that if you take 50 years and no matter how much less than that, then you will
get this much premium at this rate, the rest you
can read it on the police skin by washing, now in this plan
you also get loyalty edition, whatever you
get, you will get loyalty edition only when you have paid the full premium on time by
adopting the full premium payment,
otherwise you will not get the
loyalty edition now  That you get on Salman, you will
get one percent of your annual advisory benefit which is income benefit. If the premium is less than Rs 1.5 lakh,
then you will get 22% of the annual income benefit.
This is loyalty addition. If you
analyze if the premium is
from Rs 1.5 lakh to Rs 3 lakh but less than Rs 3 lakh, then
3.5 percent is the premium of Rs 3 lakh,
but if it is less than Rs 5 lakh, then 24.48 percent
and if the premium is Rs 5 lakh or more, then
25.6 percent will be given. Whose
income benefit amount will come
according to the countries, it is okay that there is no benefit.
Now, for example, let us understand, suppose
we are Mr. P, his age is 30
years, he is taking a policy term of
13 years, so with a policy system of 13 years, the
premium
payment term here is of 12 years and the advisory premium
means the basic premium of Rs 1 lakh, if it is done
here, then what will be the understanding
here  The factor will be yours,
as I just told you a while
ago, if you have watched the video carefully, then the
major news with it will be
Rs 13 lakh because your
horse will be made frill in the last,
plan option A has been taken for income benefit and the
income period is of 20 years here,
okay, now the income benefit
option that is being given here is of 20 years,
so according to that, the income benefit rate is
how much, 125 percent as told to you
or it will be applied on this, it will be
applied on advisory premium, the
rate of loyalty addition is 22%, this loyalty
addition rate will be applied on income benefit,
which will be clearly okay, now we
know here how much will be the airline [ __ ] benefit, after
adding the total loyalty addition, which will be the
first installment, that will also be the income benefit plus
loyalty addition, that will be the first installment, including the
lottery addition of income benefit, so without
Loyalty addition which will
be the first installment, I know that we will
take out 125 percent of our basic premium because its
rate is 125 percent when the income benefit was
1 lakh, if we take out 125 percent
then it will ask for 1 lakh 25 thousand rupees, the
rate of loyalty addition here is 22%, so
22 percent of 125000 will be taken out here, it will come to
70 rs.27500, so the first
installment which will be income benefit plus
loyalty addition, if we add both of them here then
that amount will be
1 lakh 52 thousand ₹500, I will keep getting it continuously for the next 20 years,
right, so
what will be our total income, after
adding loyalty addition, what is the income tax for 20 years, so
what will we do, in our first
installment, we will add 20 here *, that
means if we add the amount of income *,
then the total form of income benefit will be
1 lakh  If we invest 20% in 52 thousand 500
then 30 lakh 50 thousand will be generated
in 12 years. How much premium have we offered? We have offered
₹1200000. Now this information which
I have told you here as an example is based on the
rates available in the quality document
which I shared with you.
Now the video is long so
in the next lesson we will understand Income with Written on Premium
option along with example, Loan
Surrender Value and other important features which are the
benefits.